Now the Video tab,
which is very simple.
First you'll need one or two
already rendered images of
your project.
I'll use this project here as
an example.
In here we have two fields,
the Initial Frame and the Final Frame.
You can load two images at once,
or just one image in the Initial
Frame.
And if you want,
in this option you can choose
the video with audio or
without audio.
You can also pick some preset
settings for your video.
If you want a transition from
one image to another, you'll need
to load both images.
Now if you just want to create
movement, load a single image in
the Initial Frame.
In this example we'll use one
image during the day and another
at night, and ask the tool to create
a timelapse.
It's important to write in
the text field what you're imagining
for your video.
If you leave it blank,
the AI may not understand
exactly what you want to create.
Now in this example,
I'll show you how to generate
a video using only the Initial Frame.
Here you can ask the AI
to create some kind of movement, or even
add elements happening in your scene.